威尔 · 森坦斯: 但是现在，我实际上想在这里补充一些东西。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: But for now,
I actually want to add something here.
我想要一点奖金，和我们刚才看到的有关。
I want a little bonus here,
related to what we just saw.
我想介绍箭头函数，一种保存代码的简便方法。
I want to introduce arrow functions,
a shorthand way to save our code.
让我们看看这里。
Let's have a look at this here.
我们已经得到了原始的函数定义。
We've got our original
function definition up here.
我们知道它是一个函数因为,
We know it's a function because look,
前面有个漂亮的单词功能。
it's got the beautiful word
function at the front.
在我看来，这是非常可读的。
That is, in my view, really readable.
我知道函数什么时候出现。
I know exactly when
the function's showing up.
它有一个身体，它有一个参数。
It's got a body and it's got a parameter.
当我最终运行乘以2加上一点点3时,
That when I end up running multiply
by two with a bit of three,
它会在输入端插入3。
it's going to insert three into input.
三乘二返回六进输出。
Three by two return out six into output.
还有其他方法可以保存函数。
There are other ways to save functions.
让我们看看下一个版本。
Let's look at the next version down.
这些都忽略了一个事实，那就是我们通过阅读来获得控制台。
Each of these ignore the fact that we
read acquiring a console our way through.
这不是每次的单个代码文件。
This is not the individual
files of code each time.
下一行。
Next line down.
现在我们在这里声明引入 ESX 的所谓箭头函数。
We now here declare what's known as
an arrow function introducing ESX.
记住函数定义可以被存储，分配给标签。
Remember function definitions can
be stored, assigned to labels.
因为它们只是场景背后的物体
Because they're just objects
behind the scenes, and
这正是我们现在要做的。
that's exactly what we're doing here.
我们把这个功能放在右手边
We are taking that function there on
the right hand side and storing and
标号乘以2。
label multiply by 2.
它对所有人来说都有一些差异，但就我们现在的目的而言,
It has some differences under the hood for
all, but for our purposes here for now,
我们把这个放在这里。
let's just put this here.
我们声明的第二行，乘以2。
That second line down there we declare,
multiply by 2.
就是这个。
There it is.
我们给它赋了一个函数定义。
And we assign it a function definition.
就是这样，没有变化。
There it is, no change.
现在我要说的是，我们就像在这里输入参数名一样。
Now I will say this, let's just just like
up here the parameter name is input.
你知道，让我们把它放在这里，蓝色更集中一点。
You know, let's put it here
the blue being a bit more focused.
参数名称是输入。
The parameter name is input.
但是在第二行里什么也没有改变。
But nothing has changed
in that second line.
嗯，JavaScript 的设计者喜欢减少代码。
Well, the designers of
JavaScript love to reduce code.
我喜欢把它想象成一种渴望
I like to think of this
as being a desire for
易读性，但可能不是为了易读性，易读性。
legibility, but maybe not for
readability, legibility.
这使得它很好，很短，写的东西很少。
This makes it nice and
short and less stuff written.
这使得它更清晰易读。
That is makes it more legible.
我可以从字面上理解，这样可以减少阅读量，而且在页面上看起来更漂亮。
I can kind of literally there's less to
read and it sort of prettier on the page.
但它可能会降低可读性。
But it may reduce readability.
就像我马上要说的。
It will be like I'll say in a second.
但是为什么呢？
But why?
但是让我们看看下一行。
But let's look at this
next line down here.
下面这一行。
This next line down here.
这里我们声明乘以2。
Here we declaring multiply by two.
我们得到了一个参数输入。
We got a parameter input.
然后右手边发生了什么？
And then what's this thing
happen on the right hand side?
如果你只能做一件事
Well, if you will function
only does one thing and
这是它的返回值，它的输出。
that is its return value, its output.
的设计者说，你知道吗？
JavaScript designers said, you know what?
实际上，我们将跳过大括号和返回关键字
We'll let you actually skip the curly
braces and the return keyword and
我们会帮你插进去的。
we'll insert those for you.
我们会自动插入。
We'll insert those automatically.
下面这一行，参数输入，箭头输入到 JavaScript
And so this next line down here, Parameter
input, arrow input by to JavaScript
在幕后，当我们运行这个乘以2的函数时。
behind the scenes, when we run that
multiply by two function is gonna insert.
在输入前返回关键字由两个。
The Return key word in
front of input by two.
我们一会儿就能看到。
We'll see that one in a second.
看看下面这个。
Look at this one below.
如果只有一个输入，我们甚至可以删除括号。
We can even remove if you've only
got one input, the parentheses.
我只是字面上说乘以2就是那个函数定义，底下那个。
I just literally say multiply by two is
that function definition, that bottom one.
但在执行方面，我们将在明天上午或
But in terms of executing we'll see
its changes in tomorrow morning or
明天下午。
tomorrow afternoon.
但就我们目前的目的而言，最终版本没有任何改变。
But for our purposes right now,
nothing has changed in that final version.
我想要执行带有参数输入的最终版本。
The point I wanna execute that final
version with the parameter input.
然后返回输入2作为它的主体,
And then return input by 2 as its body,
只是为了确保我们知道什么都没改变。
just to make sure we know
that nothing's changed.
让我们实际执行最后一个。
So let's actually execute
that final one there.
我们就在这里做吧。
Let's do it down here.
让我们宣布朝着，让我们清除最后一行的左边。
Let's declare Toward, let's clear
the left hand side of that final line.
这就对了，我乘以两个函数。
There we go.
And I multiply by two functions.
我们这里使用的是最后一个版本。
We're using the very last version here.
我们正在使用最后一个版本，甚至没有任何参数，没有花括号,
We're using that very last version,
not even any params no curly braces,
非常清晰。
super legible.
我马上告诉你们，为什么要问这个问题
And I tell you in a moment
why question it's
老实说，对读者来说，它是可读的。
honestly it's readability in terms
of its meaning to the reader.
因为有很多民间人士会观看这个节目，这是一样的
Because there are many folk people will
be watching this going that's the same
顶端的东西。
thing as at the top.
我的意思是，这是我们如何使用它的一个隐藏的改变，但不是在这一点上。
I mean, it's an under the hood changes for
how we use it but not at this point.
但本质上还是一样的。
And yet it's essentially the same.
所以是的，托德。
So yeah, Todd.
现在我们用左手边。
Let's now use the left hand side there.
我们首先宣布什么？
What are we declaring first?
音箱2: 恒定输出。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Constant output.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，非常好，我们现在就要开始了
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, excellent,
and we've gotta go ahead now and
运行什么功能？
run what function?
演讲者2: 乘以2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Multiply By2.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 乘以2，再一次，人们，只是真的很清楚,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: MultiplyBy2, and
again, people, just be really clear,
我们运行的是最底层的那个，输入什么，托德？
we're running the very bottom one,
with the input of what, Todd?
讲者2:3 威尔 · 森特斯: 3，全新的什么，托德,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: 3.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 3, brand-new what, Todd,
有什么变化吗，全新的？
any change, no, brand-new?
演讲者2: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Execution context.
执行上下文，它就是它本来的样子。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
it is what it is.
这就是全新的执行环境，我们开始了。
There it is, brand new execution context,
and into we go.
我们当地的记忆中,
What's in our local memory,
首先传入本地内存的值是多少，托德？
what's the value passed into
our local memory first, Todd?
说话人2: 输入，值为3。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Input, value of 3.
是否命题: 值3分配给什么参数？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Value of 3
assigned to what parameter?
讲者二: 输入法 输入，还有什么变化吗,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Input.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Input, any change yet,
人们？
people?
演讲者2: 没有 威尔 · 森坦斯: 不。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Nope.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Nope.
那么，这个函数的主体是什么？
Now, what's the body of that function?
箭头右边有一个插入的单词。
It's a stuff on the right hand side
of the arrow with an inserted word.
我要做的是,
I'm going to do in,
我知道，我要用什么词来表达我的紫色，汤姆？
I know, I'm gonna do in purple
here with what inserted word, Tom?
讲者二: 报税表。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Return.
句子: 回到前面的代码是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Return
in front of what code?
讲者2:3乘以2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: 3 times 2.
是的，输入2，也就是3乘2，也就是6。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, input by 2,
which is 3 by 2, which is 6.
然后再返回到输出中，就是这样。
And that is then return out
into output and there it is.
你可能会看着然后离开，是的，我知道。
You maybe watching and
then go, yeah, I knew that.
但是我想让我看看下面的东西，输入2的箭头输入。
But I think let me see that stuff
down there, input arrow input by 2.
它看起来非常类似于等号赋值,
And it looks so similar to an assignment,
by the equals sign,
我向你们保证，人们看到的是右手边的那一面。
I promise you people are seeing
that right-hand side there.
没有意识到这是一个完整的函数定义，带有一个参数和
And not realizing that is a full function
definition, with a parameter and
一具尸体，并自动为我们插入返回语句，好吗？
a body, with a return statement
inserted automatically for us, okay?
你会马上做点什么吗，让我们看看这个
Would you do something in a second is
actually let's have a look at this in
练习。
practice.
看看这个，我用了一个高阶函数
So look at this,
I've taken a higher order function and
的回调函数。
callback function from just before.
你看，我把乘以2的函数改成了箭头样式。
And you see I've changed the function
multiply by 2 into the arrow style.
有什么变化吗？
Has anything changed?
什么都没有改变，我把代码插入。
Nothing's changed,
I take that code I insert it.
在年，我用它作为指示，我会采取一个重置零
In, I use it as instructions,
I would take a reposition zero
这将是插入指令的第一个。
which will be the number one
on inserted into instructions.
也就是把它插入到每个人身上乘以2。
Which is inserting it into
everybody multiply by two.
一个在井中，一个在输入的本地内存中
One is going to then be in the well one
would be in the local memory of the input
参数值参数和。
parameters value argument and.
然后我们做1乘2，然后返回2到执行中
And then we do 1 by 2 and
return out 2 into the execution
的上下文，并将其推送到输出。
context of copyArrayManipulate,
and push it into output.
这里什么都没有改变，但是你会越来越多地看到这种风格。
Nothing has changed here, folk, but
you're gonna see this style more and more.
还有更多,
And it gets even more,
你可能知道接下来会发生什么，看看这个。
Extreme you probably know what's coming,
have a look at that.
这就是你经常看到的景象,
This is what you end up
seeing a lot of the time,
因为我在全局函数中保留了乘以2的结果。
given that I'm saving the multiply
by two function here in global.
然后抓住它，就像丹在标签上说的那样，把它拉出来
And then just grabbing it referring to
it as Dan said by his label to pull it
进入版权操纵开发商去，你知道吗？
into copyright manipulate Developers go,
you know what?
最好还是跳过这一步，直接编写代码
Might as well just skip that step,
might as well just take the code and
直接插进去。
insert that in directly.
在执行上下文中，我们不使用标签乘以2
Given that we don't use the label multiply
by 2 inside of the execution context of
操纵。
manipulate.
我们只需要使用代码给它一个新的标签指令,
We just use the code And
give it a new label instructions,
为什么还要给它贴上标签，然后插进去？
why even bother giving it a label and
inserting it?
为什么不直接抓取代码并在内部使用它呢？
Why not just grab the code and
just use it inside?
事实就是这样，但是
And that's exactly what happens, but
当你看到那行代码时，我们很想知道。
when you see that line of code there,
we are so tempted to feel that.
这个函数就在这里执行
That function is being kind
of executed right there and
那就不清楚它在做什么。
then it's so unclear what it's doing.
但是这里有乘以2的完整函数定义,
But that there is the full function
definition of multiply by two,
就是上面的函数定义。
which is that function
definition up there.
现实中什么都没有改变。
Nothing has changed in reality.
我们知道的那个函数定义通过名称和
That function definition we
know we grabbed by name and
插入使用的劳动指令。
inserted engaged the labor instructions.
什么都没变。
Nothing's changed.
我们也遇到过同样的情况
We've taken exactly the same situation,
and
我们现在已经插入了整个函数。
we've now just inserted
the whole function.
我可以采取这个输入箭头输入二和
I could take this input
arrow input by two and
只是这个代码现在直接插入了。
it's just this code now inserted directly.
好吧，如果你想对此表示赞同，你会经常看到这个
All right, if you wanna have thumbs on
this, you're gonna see this a lot and
我马上就会给出我对这种方法的看法。
I'm gonna give my view on
this approach in a second.
但你把我弄糊涂了。
But you lost me.
我清楚的澄清真的感兴趣的任何人的澄清
I'm clear clarification of really
interested in anyone's clarification on
因为这是一个具有挑战性的转变。
this cuz this is a challenging shift here.
好吧，我们今天不打算过多地使用这种风格，但是
Okay, we're not gonna tend to use
this style too much today, but
这是越来越标准的风格，为什么没有人使用它太多的一天。
this is increasingly A standard style,
why nobody use it too much a day.
因此，在我们的函数中使用匿名，可以立即提高代码的易读性。
So, anonymous in our functions, they
improve immediate legibility of the code.
让它看起来很漂亮，对吧？
It makes it look like kind of pretty,
right?
我没有把东西分开存放。
I'm not storing stuff separately.
为什么我在做难的部分的时候总是这样？
Why am i so when i'm doing hard parts?
为什么我，喜欢声明函数分开,
Why do I,
Like declare function separately,
而实际上只是直接插入。
when in reality will tend to
just insert them directly.
这是一个反问，但好吧，凯尔，继续。
It was a rhetorical question,
but okay, Kyle, go ahead.
说话人3: 你可能还有另外一个函数需要传递。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You might have another
function where you want to pass.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我喜欢这个，这是一个很好的理由。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I love that,
that's a very good reason.
对我来说，我更倾向于用我猜想的，教育学的意义来说，我这样做是因为
For me, I'm sort of talking in a more I
guess, pedagogical sense, I do it because
这样可以提高易读性，我们写的代码更少，也许看起来更漂亮。
while this improves legibility, we write
less code, it looks prettier, perhaps.
因此，这是非常标准的。
And therefore it is very standard.
而且我非常标准，完全支持它,
And I'm very standard and
full endorsement of it,
当我解释这些概念的时候。
in terms of when I'm
explaining these concepts.
这是一个很好的预测器，从某种意义上来说，它是否可读
And that's a good predictor of
whether it's readable in a sense of
开发人员可以理解和理解。
understandable and
comprehensible for the developers.
顺便说一句，我不是说你不应该这么做。
And by the way, this is not me
saying that you shouldn't do this.
这是非常标准的，这绝对是边界线更好的做法。
It's very standard, it's absolutely
border line better practice.
但就我们的理解而言。
But in terms of our understanding.
在决定它的实际工作方式方面,
In terms of deciding how
it's actually working,
我会区分易读性和可读性。
I would distinguish between legibility and
readability.
这在引擎盖下是如何理解的，这在引擎盖下是如何工作的
How this is understanding under the hood,
how is this working under the hood is
对了解真正发生的事情至关重要。
vital to understand
what's really happening.
这个函数，传入的整个定义，更容易追踪
That function, whole definition that's
being passed in is much easier to track
当我们按照标签声明时，就会发生这种情况。
that that's happening when
we've declared it by label.
用关键字函数再把它传递进去。
With the key word function and
then pass it in.
这就是为什么我们今天要继续艰难的部分,
And that's why we're going to
continue in hard part today,
主要使用关键字功能。
to mostly use the keyword function.
这个设计，这个函数的简化版本，实际上是,
And this design here, this little
shorthand version of functions, is really,
当你传递一些小函数时，非常好的易读性。
really nice for legibility when
you're passing little mini functions.
在是其他功能的输入有真正的可读性和充分认可和
In is the input to other functions there
is really readable and fully endorse and
我绝对想让你知道，你会看到有一个标准。
I would absolutely you know,
you will see there's a standard.
但是我们不应该总是使用箭头函数。
But it's not automatically the case that
we should always be using arrow functions.
我们稍后会看到你们在这种情况下完全撤销什么
And we'll see you later on situations in
which you will completely under undo what
我们想要达到的目标。
we're trying to achieve.
对于箭的功能有一个隐藏的改变。
There is an under the hood change
to how arrow functions treat.
这个关键词作业，我们会在课程中看到
This key word assignment that we're
going to see in our courses and
原型会议，它可以是真正有用的。
prototypes session where
it can be really useful.
顺便说一下，我现在告诉你这个小预览，如果他是一个方法中的一个函数,
By the way, I tell you this little preview
now if he was a function inside a method,
这个词汇范围的箭头函数是他是一个多伦多，我可以真正
that lexically scoped arrow function was
he was a Toronto where I can be really
有用的。
useful.
但是如果你把它用在对象的常规方法上，它就不起作用了。
But if you're using that for regular
methods on objects, It ain't gonna work.
所以我们将继续使用默认的函数声明样式。
So we're gonna continue to default
to the function declaration style.
但是当我们解析小婴儿函数的时候,
But, for when we're parsing
little baby functions in,
我确实支持这样的说法，即地图数组123。
I do endorse that that makes it,
that says map array 123.
我们把每个元素乘以2。
So we take each element,
and multiply it by 2.
看到这一行了吗？
And see that one in one line?
真不错，我很喜欢。
That is pretty nice, I do like that.
但是为了理解它是如何在引擎盖下工作的,
But in understanding how
it's working under the hood,
了解这里到底发生了什么，这一点越来越重要。
it's important ever more to understand
what's really happening here.
好的，杰森，说吧。
Okay, Jason go ahead.
演讲者2: 是，[咳嗽]对不起，有没有记忆或者
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is, [COUGH] excuse me,
are there any memory or
内联策略的内存分配节省。
memory allocation savings for
that strategy of inlining.
在这里你不需要创建一个外部的全局上下文
Where you instead of creating
an external global context for
在内存中存储 multipyBy2的函数。
A function to store multipyBy2 in memory.
威尔 · 森特斯: 杰森，这件事,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The thing with that,
Jason,
只是我们在这里讨论的是，在任何时刻，这么小的记忆增加或减少。
is just that we're talking here about such
small memory gains or losses at any point.
我们生活的世界并不是建立在这样的事情上的。
We don't live in the world where we're
constructed on that sort of thing.
现在，如果你递归地调用这个函数，如果你是，并且
Now, if you were calling that function
recursively, if you were, and
我们明天在原型课上会看到。
we'll see tomorrow in class in prototypes.
将100个函数保存到1000个对象中，每个对象都会被复制。
Saving a 100 functions to 1,000
objects where each of them is copied.
我们只需要一组函数
Where we could just have
one set of functions and
都指向同一组函数。
point all to that same set of functions.
是的，这就是性能的重要性，这里的这类事情就是这样
Yeah, that's where performance counts,
this sort of thing here it's so
我们不需要担心的小事。
minor that we don't need to worry.
作为一个开发者，越来越多的最有价值的资源,
More and more the most valuable
resource as a developer,
是开发商的时间和推理能力。
is the developer's time and
ability to reason about it.
相反，我们最终会自动收集垃圾
Versus do we end up automatically
garbage collecting and
因此，在那一刻保存一些记忆？
therefore, in the moment
saving some memory?
在这些边缘情况下，可读性是第一位的。
On these marginal cases,
readability comes first.
话虽如此只要你明白这里的情况,
That being said, as long as you
understand how this is working here,
直接传入这个函数吗？
passing in that function directly?
我觉得它真的很不错。
I think it does it really nice.
映射，1,2,3通过这个映射规则,
Mapping, 1, 2, 3 by this mapping rule,
我认为人们不知道它是如何工作的。
where it's explicitly in that line I
think people don't know how it's working.
但是我认为人们有一种感觉，如果他们不知道怎么做，他们可以让它工作
But I think people get a sense, they can
make it work if they don't understand how
它在引擎盖下工作。
it's working under the hood.
但是我们想成为那些了解它是如何运作的人
But we wanna be those people who
understand how it's working under
引擎盖，希望现在我们做到了。
the hood, and hopefully now we do.